A celebrity is a person who has the ability to perform.
When I think about it, I feel that we are welcoming such a person today.
So, this is our guest.
Yes, sir.
I'm Hana Kojima of Amefurashi, and I'm the one who conquers the gays.
I was going to repeat what I just said. Surprisingly, I didn't remember.
I didn't remember anything. I'm sorry. I was going to say something.
I was going to say something, but I couldn't remember anything.
But I only remembered the "gay" part.
I made a mistake.
Well, that's fine. You can try even if it's just a rough sketch.
That's important, especially for idols.
Really?
If there's one thing idols and comedians have in common...
If there's one thing that idols and comedians have in common, it's that when you ask them to do something, they can't do it.
That's the point.
I think that the people who say "Do it" are the ones who end up doing it.
I wanted everyone to see that kind of attitude.
The other day, I went all the way to Yokohama Arena.
I made a big event of having dozens of idols perform 10 different kinds of events.
It was a big event for us.
It was fun. It was a lot of fun.
I'm glad you said that.
Some people said it was a lot of pressure.
I felt like I had to express myself in this short performance.
I had to express myself in this short performance.
Some people said it was a lot of pressure.
Mr. Kojima had the pleasure of having people see his ability to do something different from singing and dancing.
It was a joy.
It was fun.
But I was really nervous about the kendama.
I mean, this is my own kendama right now.
I brought my own kendama at that time, too.
But this is for the certification test.
I prepared official kendama for other people separately.
Of course, Kojima-san wasn't cheating.
He was using the one he was comfortable with.
That's right.
I really wanted to use the one I've been playing with for a long time.
So I let him use it.
But since I brought my own kendama...
I had to succeed, right?
I was so nervous, wasn't I?
I had such a shiny golden sword ball with me.
If he failed, it would have been like, what is he doing?
The pressure was like Masaaki Sakai at New Year's, wasn't it?
That's right.
You said you didn't understand.
There was something like that back then.
During the New Year's hidden trick contest.
I don't know why.
You know?
Yes, yes, yes.
You know that kind of thing?
The other day...
I was doing my impersonation of a tablecloth puller.
I was just watching YouTube or something.
I just happened to be there.
Nowadays, there is a phenomenon that comedians are learning more and more about various things
I sometimes see a phenomenon that comedians are getting to know as much as professionals
I sometimes see this phenomenon.
Do you feel like you're in this weird cycle?
No, I'm an idol.
I don't know about mediocre.
That's right.
I do a lot of research on current idols.
I do a lot of research.
It's a mysterious cycle that's starting to turn, isn't it?
Yes, I've been to many eras.
If you think about it...
I take kendama for granted.
Why do idols play Kendama? I'm just saying.
I'm asking myself this...
There was an event called "open rehearsal" at Amegrasi.
and a professional kendama player taught me how to play kendama.
I was one of the most promising members.
I was the one with the most potential.
So we started to play kendama for 100 days.
That's how I got better.
I know that kendama improves if you do it hard for 100 days.
If you play kendama hard for 100 days
Did you think about whether you would be able to advance as an idol or not?
Everything is a challenge.
I thought I should learn everything.
Performers are people who have the ability to do what they do.
I think you are definitely pursuing a career in show business.
Yes, I am a performer.
And you didn't succeed in Yokohama Arena, a place with a lot of pressure.
And you were able to pull it off, weren't you?
Yes, it was a success.
And besides that, I've done some illustrations.
I mean, there's a close difference.
It's obvious that the design is at a level where it could be made into a product as it is.
Thank you very much.
I had a little bit of an image in mind for that one.
I'm not very good at drawing characters.
I'm not very good at drawing characters, but I often draw people.
I often draw people, but for this project, the theme was the characters of the STAPLA idols, right?
So I think everyone will probably come with a character, like a cot.
I dared to draw human-like characters.
It's a virtual illustration by Mr. Yoshida, isn't it?Mr. Yoshida's virtual illustrations, right?
I thought it would be a good idea to collaborate with them.
You went to all that trouble?
It's a shame we didn't have more time to talk about it, though.
That's true.
But I thought it would be great if we could collaborate with that virtual illustration someday.
I thought it would be nice to collaborate with a virtual character someday.
Anyway, I'm glad you took the time to understand that I'm doing something like that.
I'm glad you took the trouble to understand that I'm doing that.
You like to talk, don't you?
I guess so.
You like to prepare things, don't you?
I think you have to prepare for everything.
I want to be an idol because I want to be on stage.
I like to stand out, but the preparation is a pain in the ass.
I like to stand out, but it's a job for people who don't want to be bothered with preparation.
The staff will take care of all the arrangements, and you don't have to worry.
It's like an idol who says, "Don't worry, I'll take care of it, and I'll decide what to do.
I like it from the very beginning.
I love it.
I don't know if I should say I love it, but...
You are a creator, aren't you?
That's true.
I love what I create.
I think you are the creator of idols.
In this case, I'd like to say that I enjoyed the artistic part of the show.
It's hard to find someone who enjoyed it so positively.
Or monoboke, although there were a lot of other strong people there.
The quality of the monoboke was also very high.
Really? I'm glad.
Akira was 100%, wasn't he?
I also did the female version.
It's a difficult balance to do.
But you finished it and came back.
In a big venue like Yokohama Arena.
I think I told you that it took a lot of courage to do Akira 100% in such a big venue like Yokohama Arena.
I think I was a little nervous after Hiccarl's performance.
I think we were a little nervous after Hiccarl.
I'm sorry to say that the quality of the performance was not that great.
I'm sorry, but it's like a comedian's anti-ministry after appearing on Tunnels.
I'm not a comedian.
I'm not a comedian, but that's the quality of the show.
But the members were backstage watching us.
They got really excited.
When Tanada did his monologue.
They laughed so hard.
You have it?
I can't show it to you.
It's amazing that there's some kind of footage of the audience.
That's right.
Abefrasseh, you're a team of enigmatic people.
Abbey Flashy, they all have their own unique personalities.
And when they perform...
They've been doing things lately that remind me of K-pop.
And they're all physically strong.
That's right.
So the gap between the two is pretty amazing.
Fans have told me that it's amazing how much of a gap there is.
The gap between our daily conversation and the live performance is amazing.
Abefulasi is famous for that.
That's right.
No matter when you see this and that...
There is a gap between this and that.
No matter where you go.
Wherever you go, there is a gap.
In other words, where is the essence?
It's like, "What is the essence?
The essence of a live performance is to do the hardest possible thing.
It was amazing this time, wasn't it?
Yokohama Arena
Abbey Flashy again!
They performed a new song for the first time at the StarPlaza festival.
Was that right?
Yes, the song "Fly Out" was performed for the first time at StarPlaza Fest.
It was the first time we performed it at StarPlaza Fest.
No one knew about it, but it was very popular.
It was really popular.
It was so exciting and cool.
The next song, Michi, is also very cool.
It's a song that everyone can enjoy.
It's a cute song.
The song "Drop Drop" is also one of Abbey Flushy's representative songs.
It is one of the most popular songs of Abbey Flushy.
There was a lot of excitement!
We presented three songs that showcased the current Abbey Flushie.
That's all we've been doing.
We've done a lot of gory live performances, monoboke, illustrations, and kendama.
And in Kojima's case, one more thing.
You're doing another one, right?
Yes, I am.
And this Namie Joshi Hatsukumiai?
Harima-san was in it before.
Harima-san had already buried her joy.
You came out after she cried and said she was going to do it alone, right?
Yes, that's right.
So when Harima cried...
We all left together? I'd like to get her out.
I'd like to get out there and sing with her, wouldn't you?
But...It was like...
But of course, that's Harima's stage.
We couldn't go on the stage, but
But after that, when we appeared at the first union of Namie Girls
I thought it was so cute when Harima cried.
And we have a strong senior named Garlin who supports us
Garrin, a strong senior member of Namie, supported us.
I thought we were able to do what we always do because of her support.
When Harima-san came out...
I saw her hugging Kojima-san, didn't I?
Whenever Harima cries, she hugs me.
Maybe it's because we're next to each other in the MC position.
It's not like we have some kind of passionate agreement.
Not at all.
I heard them talking earlier.
I didn't hear anything like that at all.
Maybe it's because we're next to each other.
Maybe because we're next to each other.
Like with the strap?
Something like that.
It's like, "Oh, there it is.
Ah...
It's just that the quality of the performance is different from your previous ones.
Is it?
Yes, it is.
The direction of Amehara and Namie is the complete opposite.
I was a bit confused at first.
I've always been a cool type of person, and I'm always trying to dress in my own way.
I've always done the cool type.
Nami has a cute girl's sense of style.
I was a bit confused at first.
But as I watched Arline's back, I realized that I should do it this way.
I thought, "I see, I can do it this way.
I was able to switch to a cute style.
About Mr. Sasaki...
You're not the type to keep adding new tricks to your repertoire.
You're not that type of person, are you?
No, I'm not.
Arline is great.
I know he's great.
I know he's great, but there's so much I can learn from him.
Which aspects do you learn from?
I guess you could say that.
He always brings back goodies.
Hey, hey, hey!
That's something I can learn from.
I feel like I have to pass that on to the next generation.
I'm sure the person who brought the gift is happy.
That he's so happy.
That's because he saw Arline's back.
He took all the gifts home with him.
That's the first thing he's learning.
That's the best part.
Is there anything you can learn outside?
Watching the backs of performers out there.
Like, "Wow, you're a great performer.
You're a great performer.
Yes, I think so.
At any time.
At lunch time.
You let the younger students take it first.
I think that's really
I think it's a very touching thing to do.
It sounds like a nice thing to say.
You don't think that's true?
If it were me...
I already love food.
I'm thrilled to be a junior! Seniors first!
You're the senior first! I said, "Come on!
But Aaryn let me take the juniors first.
That's right.
That's what he said.
It was the other day.
You and Yutichan did this once, right?
After I stood you up.
When we went out one more time...
You got mad about it all, didn't you?
That's right.
I was so sorry.
It was my money.
I ate more and more.
But the truth is... if I did that, I'd be so thrilled.
You won't do it, will you?
I'll do it!
If I had my lunch, I would!
Mr. Sasaki, who watches the coach's videos, is also wonderful.
We'll take care of it.
I'm sorry, but I feel like I just heard something that doesn't have much to do with our future policy.
No, it's important!
In a way, you have a lot of skills, don't you, Kojima-san?
I see.
What do you want to do next?
Next? But I'd still like to appear on "All Night Nippon".
I'd like to appear on it.
You want to go on All Night Nippon?
I'd love to be on All Night Nippon with Ms. Yoshida.
I'm fine either way.
Really?
I'm not doing "All Night Nippon" now, am I?
I see.
We should definitely do it together.I'd love to do an All Night Nippon with you two.
I'd like to do an all-night call.
Why?
Because All Night Nippon is great.
I've never been popular, so I'd like to do it.
I'd like to say "All Night Nippon.
I get that a lot from comedians.
I'd like to do All Night Nippon.
That's what I want to do.
If I were an idol, I'd want to participate in the Tokyo Girls Festival.
I think they mean "I want to participate in Tokyo Girls Festival.
With idols in mind, do you still want to do the All Night Nippon?
Yes, of course.
There are many legends like Kyoho Nekoizumi.
I'd like to go there too.
You sound like a radio personality.
That's the first time I've been told that.
I can't go on like this.
For example, if I say I have to do a live broadcast tomorrow, and I have to unpack for how many minutes...
I don't mean something I've done before.
I'm not the type of person who'd want to do something like, "Okay, I'm going to go eat some spicy ramen I've never had before.
You're the type of person who wants to do something like that, aren't you?
Yes, I am.
That's the kind of job they're looking for now, isn't it?
Maybe that's what I want to do.
I'd love to do something with you.
If you work with me, you might break your arm during a live broadcast.
Did that happen?
Why are your eyes shining?
I'm a little curious.
It did happen.
Not at all.
If you give me a month to heal...
I did it myself.
That's true.
When I was on the air during a live broadcast event.
I heard that Remi was at home.
What do you mean?
I did it to surprise you.
The moment you heard that... your expression changed from "No, I don't want to" to "I want to try it.
I'd like to try it.
You want to try?
I'd like to enter Yoshida-san's house too.
That's something you'll do as soon as you say it.
Really?
I'm already talking with Kojima-san at this very moment.
Do you think it's any wonder Ichikawa-san's there?
It's certainly possible.
It's possible.
It's all right, isn't it?
I think that's why they're letting me on the air today.
That's what I'm thinking.
You're basically an entertainer.
Yes, I'm an idol to make people happy.
An idol to make people happy.
Then, what are your goals for the future?
Can you tell us about your future goals?
My future goal is to work with Mr. Yoshida.
Don't worry, I really want someone to make an "aikagui" for me.
I'd like you all to get me an "aikagui" so I can visit Mr. Yoshida's house.
I'll visit your house.
Please look forward to it!
You know, when we get demolished like this...
My wife is the one who invites them in.
That's right.
The other day, our daughter was on the air.
The whole family was there.
The whole family was there, and no one knew I was there.
That's great.
I'm easily fooled.
You're easy to fool, aren't you, Yoshida-kun?
That's not true.
I'm more suspicious than I thought.
I'm the type of person who suspects.
Do you often fall for surprises?
I've never been caught in a surprise.
I mean, I've never had anyone do it to me.
Surprises.
Maybe it's here in the back.
Back here, back here.
I'm surprised I didn't fall for it.
I might react normally.
You don't want to do reaction tricks. You want to do tricks.
I'd rather do tricks.
You want to set things up.
I think I'm going to write a script for the stage someday.
Are you saying that much?
I'm a creator.
I'll do my best.
Thank you very much, Anna Kojima.
Thank you very much.